（当你怀孕时，你该期待什么）
你知道怀孕的时候…
Did you know that during pregnancy..
你的手指会肿成两倍大 而且再也不会消了吗？
your fingers swell up to twice their size and never go back?
天啊，让我看看
Oh,my God! Let me see that.
你每次都会上当
You fall for it every time.
我把我的旧孕妇装 拿来给你
Hey! I brought you my old maternity clothes.
菲比，那真的是太棒了 好可爱喔！
Oh,Pheebs,that's so sweet. Oh,those are so cute!
你看，宝宝越长越大 它们也会跟着撑开来
Look. See how they expand as the baby grows?
宝宝出生后 可以穿它去偷西瓜
And after the baby's born they're great for shoplifting melons.
太好了，你们都在 感恩节，明天四点
Good,you're all here. Thanksgiving,4:00.
你猜我邀请了谁？ 还记得高中同学威尔卡佛特吗？
Guess who I invited? Remember Will Culvert from high school?
-不 -他跟罗斯同班
-No. -He was in Ross' class.
他是仪仗队的，有点胖 他是个大胖子
Marching band,was kind of overweight. Really overweight.
我属于他瘦朋友那一群
I was his thin friend.
我不记得 你是说你假想的男朋友吗？
I don't remember. Are you talking about your imaginary boyfriend?
不，那是贾拉德
No,that was Jared.
我好久 没有想起他了
Wow. Haven't thought about him in a long time.
威尔来这里出差，他没地方可去 所以我邀请他过来
Will's here on business,and he didn't have a place to go,so I invited him here.
-那很好啊 -他减肥成功
-That's nice. -Oh,he's lost a bunch of weight.
他看起来很不错 好吧，他真的是帅呆了
He looks good. Okay,I mean really gorgeous.
-我还爱着钱德 -偶尔说一下不会要你命的
-I still love Chandler. -Wouldn't hurt you to say it once in a while.
先说好了 今年我不煮火鸡…
Just so you know,I'm not gonna make a turkey this year..
-什么？ -菲比不吃火鸡
-What? -Phoebe doesn't eat turkey.
-菲比 -火鸡是漂亮聪明的动物
-Phoebe! -Turkeys are beautiful,intelligent animals.
不是的 它们既丑又笨，也很好吃
No,they're not! They're ugly and stupid and delicious!
而且吃火鸡是传统
Plus,eating them is like a tradition.
这得回溯至第一次过感恩节时 印第安人跟牛仔坐在一起
It goes back to the first Thanksgiving when the lndians sat down with the cowboys.
对，那个时候 他们在普利茅斯岩办牛仔表演
Oh,right. That's when they had that big rodeo at Plymouth Rock.
不只是菲比，威尔还在节食 钱德不吃感恩节食物…
It's not just Phoebe. Will's still on a diet,Chandler doesn't eat Thanksgiving food..
-瑞秋对家禽类反胃 -是吗？
-Rachel's having her aversion to poultry. -She is?
对，记得吗？ 那天你吃鸡肉时我得走开
Yeah. Remember? I had to leave the other day when you had that chicken.
我以为那是因为 我手里…
I thought that was because I put the whole thing..
拿着鸡要它在桌上走的关系
on my hand and made it walk across the table.
为了三个人做一只火鸡太不划算了 那真的很费功夫
It's not worth it to make a whole turkey for just three people. It's a lot of work.
但感恩节一定要吃火鸡啊
But you gotta have turkey on Thanksgiving!
感恩节不吃火鸡 就像国庆日不吃苹果派
Thanksgiving with no turkey is like Fourth of July with no apple pie.
或是星期五不吃两个披萨
Or Friday with no two pizzas.
好吧，如果它真的对你很重要 但到时候一定会剩下很多
Fine,if it means that much to you. But there's gonna be a ton left over.
不，我发誓我会把那只火鸡吃完
No. I promise I will finish that turkey.
你是说你可以一次 吃掉一整只火鸡？
You're telling me you can eat almost an entire turkey in one sitting?
没错，因为我是崔比亚尼家的人 这是我们的专长
That's right. Because I'm a Tribbiani! This is what we do.
我们不是伟大的思想家 或世界领袖…
We may not be great thinkers or world leaders..
我们书念的不多，跑不快 但该死，我们是大胃王
we don't read a lot or run fast,but damn it,we can eat!
本集播出：谣言
The.One.With.The.Rumour
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
主演：寇妮考克斯
主演：丽莎库卓
主演：麦特勒布兰
主演：马修派瑞
主演：大卫修蒙
第四次长传，第三次18码
Four wide receivers. On third and 18.
明年桌边会坐一个宝宝 感觉真的很奇怪吧？
Isn't it weird how next year there will be a baby at the table?
我是指瑞秋的孩子 但我很高兴你还有在听我说话
Rachel's. But good to know where you're at.
-嘿 -嘿
-Hey! -Hey!
-感恩节快乐 -你也是
-Happy Thanksgiving. -You too!
-需要我帮忙吗？ -好啊
-Can I help? -Yes.
通常钱德会帮忙 但他看球赛看得正入迷
Chandler usually helps,but he's into the game.
麻烦你帮忙折餐巾 我要去对面看看土豆泥好了没
Could you fold these napkins? I'm gonna go across the hall to check on the yams.
不，亲爱的，不是那样的
No,sweetie. No,not like that.
我们不是在办农场舞会
We're not at a barn dance.
把它们折成天鹅的形状 我在圣诞节时教过你，记得吗？
Fold them like swans. I showed you at Christmas. Remember?
记得，一切历历在目
Yeah,it all just came screaming back to me.
-球赛还好看吗？ -我不知道
-So how's the game? -I have no idea.
-什么？ -我假装看球赛…
-What? -I'm pretending to watch..
那样子就不必帮忙
so I don't have to help out.
我不敢相信 这招太高明了
I don't believe you! That is brilliant!
-莫妮卡不知道？ -对
-And Monica has no idea? -No.
偶尔 我会对着电视大叫
Once in a while,I just yell stuff at the TV.
嘿，什么？啊
Hey! What? Aw! Hey!
-你的球队赢了吗？ -安德森刚刚又得分了
-Your team winning? -Anderson just scored again.
根本就没有安德森这号人物
There is no Anderson.
我也想如法炮制，莫妮卡
I wanna get in on this. Hey,Mon?
我真的没办法帮你 我不知道球赛打到哪里了
I can't help you after all. I didn't realize this game was on.
-你喜欢美式足球？ -通常我是不喜欢
-You like football? -Normally,I don't.
但今天是绿湾队在比赛
But,you know,Green Bay is playing.
-你喜欢绿湾队？ -那是我最喜欢的湾
-You like Green Bay? -It's only my favorite bay.
布拉德・皮特
Brad Pitt
-感恩节快乐 -威尔，我很高兴你能来
-Happy Thanksgiving. -Will,I'm so glad that you came.
你看起来帅呆了，你一定减掉了…
You look great. You must've lost..
150磅 我会是赛百味三明治广告的下一号人选
150 pounds. I'll be on one of those Subway commercials.
-是派 -零脂肪，无糖，也没有奶
-A pie! -It's no fat,no sugar,no dairy.
-它不好吃，丢了它 -我来介绍你们认识
-It's no good. Throw it out. -Meet some people.
他是我丈夫钱德 他是威尔
This is my husband,Chandler. This is Will.
我很想跟你握手 但我忙着看球赛
Oh,hey. I'd shake your hand but I'm really into the game.
而且我们两个只要不站在一起 就不会伤了我的自尊
Plus,it'd be better for my ego if we didn't stand next to each other.
-她是菲比 -嗨
-This is Phoebe. -Hi.
嘿，哇
Hey. Wow!
做的好
Well done.
-你要帮我吗？ -我真的觉得你很漂亮
-Wanna give me a hand? -I can't get over how great you look.
-你也很帅，你的身材真棒 -我在看球赛，但我没聋
-You look incredible too. You're so fit. -I'm watching the game,but I'm not deaf.
-我一直想告诉你，罗斯也会来 -太棒了，我喜欢罗斯
-I meant to tell you,Ross is coming. -Great,I love Ross.
很好，瑞秋格林也会来
Good. And Rachel Greene too.
-有问题吗？ -没有，没关系的
-Is there a problem? -No. It's okay.
那只是…天啊，我恨她
It's just.. God,I hated her.
-什么？ -我恨她
-What? -I hated her.
高中时她对我很凶
She was horrible to me in high school.
但那是很久以前的事了，现在我很好 或许再见到她会很有趣
But hey,that was a long time ago. I'm in a good place. Might be fun to see her again.
你有蛋糕或饼干吗？
Got any cakes or cookies or something?
不，威尔
No,Will! No!
我们很久没大叫了 或许我们该大叫一下
It's been a while since we screamed. Maybe we should.
-好吧，不！ -加油
-Oh,okay. No! -Come on!
该死的裁判，下地狱去吧！
Damn you,ref! You burn in hell!
你在做什么？ 你还得吃掉一整只火鸡
What are you doing? You've got an entire turkey to eat.
让我跟你解释一下 人体的运作方式
Let me explain to you how the human body works.
我得先让我的胃暖暖身
I have to warm up my stomach first.
-吃薯片像是在做拉筋运动 -好吧
-Eating chips is like stretching. -Okay.
-别担心，崔比亚尼永远吃不饱 -我要告诉你一件事
-Don't worry,Tribbianis never get full. -I'm here to tell you something.
你可以吃个不停 但你无法填满内心的空虚
You can eat and eat,but nothing will ever fill that void.
-这家伙到底是谁？ -他是我们的高中同学威尔，他是乔伊
-Who the hell is this guy? -This is Will,from high school. This is Joey.
-要来点薯片吗？ -不
-Want some chips? -No.
-威尔 -罗斯
-Will! -Ross!
你来了 天啊，你看起来棒极了，大帅哥
Hey,you came! Man,you look incredible! Hot stuff!
-大帅哥？ -很高兴能见到你
-Hot stuff? -It's good to see you,man.
我也是，你是做哪一行的？
Yeah. You too. So,what are you up to?
-我是期货经纪人 -听起来很有趣
-I'm a commodities broker. -That sounds interesting.
-才怪 -喔
-Yeah,it's not. -Oh.
-但我现在既有钱又苗条 -喔
-But I'm rich and thin. -Oh.
自从兰西戴维斯的毕业派对之后 我就没有见过你
I haven't seen you since Lance Davis' graduation party.
那一晚真的很疯狂
That was such a fun night.
如果我们都有被邀请就好了 但那还是很疯狂
Would've been good if we had gotten in,but still fun.
那时我们太傻了 你还记得我们居然那么喜欢恐龙吗？
We were lame. Do you remember how into dinosaurs we were?
-对 -你是做哪一行的？
-Yeah. -So,what do you do now?
你要在城里待多久？
So how long are you in town?
-嗨 -嘿，亲爱的，太好了
-Hi. -Hey,sweetie. Oh,good.
瑞秋格林
Rachel Greene.
啊，对了 你没事吧？
Oh,that's right. Are you gonna be okay?
我没事，只是… 天啊，罗斯，我恨她
Oh,I'll be fine. It's just.. God,I hate her,Ross! I hate her!
高中是很久以前的事了
High school was a long time ago.
看看她拿着土豆泥 站在那里的样子
Look at her standing there with those yams.
我的两个死对头 瑞秋格林跟碳水化合物
My two greatest enemies: Rachel Greene and complex carbohydrates.
天啊，那是谁？
Oh,my God. Who is that?
-他是我们的高中同学威尔 -我不记得他了
-That's Will,from high school. -Oh! I do not remember him.
他真的 越来越性感了
Wow,really got that sexy smoldering thing going on.
天啊 看他盯着我瞧的样子
Oh,my God. Look at the way he's just staring at me.
他用唇语跟我说话
He's trying to mouth something to me.
我恨你
I hate you!
-好了，晚餐准备好了 -好吧
-Okay,dinner's ready! -Okay!
-真的很精彩 -谁赢了？
-Solid effort. Solid effort. -Oh,so who won?
-绿湾队 -底特律队
-Green Bay. -Detroit.
-什么？ -技术上来说狮队赢了
-What? -The Lions technically won.
但在士气方面 是绿湾美人鱼队赢了
But it was a moral victory for the Green Bay Mermen.
嗨，你是威尔吧？ 嗨，我是瑞秋格林
Hi! Will,right? Right,hi. I'm Rachel Greene.
-我记得你 -真的吗？你真好
-Oh,I remember you. -Really? Aren't you sweet?
我得告诉你 我真的很难记得你的样子
I gotta tell you,I'm having the hardest time placing you.
等一下，我想我记得你
Hang on! I think I remember you.
我们在兰西戴维斯的毕业派对上 厮混过？
Did we fool around at Lance Davis' graduation party?
-你真是不可思议 -谢谢你
-You are unbelievable. -Thank you.
瑞秋，你坐这边 威尔，你坐到那边去
Rachel? Why don't you sit here? And Will,you sit way over there.
就那样？即使没有人帮我 我也可以吃掉它，没问题
That's it? Even if nobody helps me,I can eat that. No problem.
-至少给我一点挑战 -这是钱德的鸡肉
-At least give me a challenge. -This is Chandler's chicken.
这才是火鸡
This is the turkey.
那有多大呢？
Oh. How big is that?
-大约19磅 -它跟我刚出生时差不多大
-About 19 pounds. -It's like me when I was born.
-谁想吃土豆泥？威尔？ -你喜欢那样做，对吧？
-Who would like some yams? Will? -You'd like that,wouldn't you?
什么？ 拜托把鸡肉…
What? Oh,can we please keep the chicken..
跟火鸡放到另一边去
and the turkey on the other side?
-那个味道真的… -太典型了
-The smell is just.. -Typical.
-什么？ -我说那太典型了
-What? -I said it was typical.
你的典型作风，瑞秋女王 在瑞秋王国想做什么就做什么
Typical of you. Queen Rachel does whatever she wants in Rachel-land.
说真的，这家伙是谁？
Seriously,who is this guy?
抱歉，你对我有问题吗？
Sorry,do you have a problem with me?
-我不知道，我有吗？ -我想你有
-I don't know. Do I? Do I? -I think you do.
你在高中时对他有点凶
You were a little mean to him in high school.
-有点凶？你让我活在痛苦深渊 -我不知道，抱歉
-A little mean? You made my life miserable. -I had no idea. I'm sorry.
你应该抱歉的 去他的，把土豆泥拿过来给我
Well,you should be. Screw it. Bring on the yams.
但你很努力在减肥
But you worked so hard.
-土豆泥 -好的
-Yams! -Okay.
不论在高中时我对你做了什么 我都非常抱歉
I'm real sorry for whatever I did to you in high school.
不只是我，我们组了一个俱乐部
It wasn't just me. We had a club.
-你们组了一个俱乐部？ -“我恨瑞秋格林俱乐部”
-You had a club? -The "I Hate Rachel Greene Club"!
你们全都聚在一起恨我？
So you all just joined together to hate me?
-还有谁加入那个俱乐部？ -我跟罗斯
-Who else was in this club? -Me and Ross.
你不必指我 她知道罗斯是谁
No need to point. She knows who Ross is.
-你参加“我恨瑞秋俱乐部”？ -没错
-You were in an "I Hate Rachel" club? -Yes,he was.
不
No,no.
-还有谁参加了你们的俱乐部？ -那个来自泰国的交换学生
-So who else was in this club? -That exchange student from Thailand.
但我想他不知道那是怎么一回事
But I don't think he knew what it was.
你们太酷了
You guys were cool.
罗斯，我们交往了两年…
So,Ross,we went out for two years..
你没有告诉我 你参加过“我恨瑞秋俱乐部”？
and you never told me you were in an "I Hate Rachel Club"?
你跟她交往过？我们说好的
You went out with her? We had a pact.
-那不是永久的约定 -我们的确说了“永远”
-It's not like it was binding forever. -It had the word "eternity" in it.
我考虑要加入“我恨火鸡俱乐部”
I'm thinking of joining an "I Hate Turkey Club."
虽然我喜欢吃火鸡三明治
Although,I do love a turkey club.
莫妮卡，你知道这件事吗？
Monica? Did you know about this?
我不知道 所以你们才会常把房门锁上吗？
I didn't. Is that why you used to lock the bedroom door?
-对 -我得说我松了一口气
-Yeah. -A little relieved,I gotta say.
听着，瑞秋，我很抱歉，好吗？ 那时我是个愚蠢的孩子
Look,Rach,I'm sorry,okay? I was a stupid kid,okay?
-我会加入俱乐部是因为… -是一起成立
-The only reason I joined.. -Cofounded.
一起成立
Cofounded.
我会一起成立那个俱乐部 因为我那时疯狂地爱着你
Cofounded the club,was that I was in love with you.
我处理的不好 如果你把“我恨瑞秋俱乐部”…
I didn't handle it very well. If you think about it,the "I Hate Rachel Club"..
想成“我爱瑞秋俱乐部”
was really the "I Love Rachel Club."
但它真的是“我恨瑞秋俱乐部”
Except that it was really the "I Hate Rachel Club."
你们一起说我的坏话？
So you'd get together and say mean things about me?
-不只是那样 -不
-We did a little more than that. -No,no,no.
你们还做了什么？
What else did you do?
-我们散布一个谣言 -什么谣言？
-We started a rumor. -What rumor?
快点，威尔 挣脱束缚告诉我们
Come on,Will,just take off your shirt and tell us.
-罗斯 -那真的没什么
-Ross? -It was no big deal.
我们说…那个谣言是…
We said that.. The rumor was that..
你同时有 男性跟女性的生殖器官
you had both male and female reproductive parts.
-什么？ -没错，我们说你爸妈…
-What? -That's right. We said your parents..
丢铜板决定把你当成女孩养大 但你还是有小鸡鸡
flipped a coin,decided to raise you as a girl,but you still had a hint of a penis.
-天啊 -那是你们编的？
-Oh,my God! -You started that?
-你也听过？ -我们学校里每个人都听过
-You heard that? -Everyone at our school heard it!
我的学校里每个人都听过 你就是那个双性啦啦队员？
Everyone at my school heard it. You were the hermaphrodite cheerleader?
不
Oh,no!
现在我终于懂了 所以亚当卡特不想跟我约会
It makes sense now. This is why Adam Carter wouldn't go out with me.
为什么比利 只想停留在这一区
Why Billy would just stay in this region.
比利成了男同志 所以那不是我们的错
Billy's gay now,so that one's not really our fault.
-你为什么不告诉我？ -我想或许那是真的
-Why didn't you tell me? -I thought it might be true.
我担心你会大哭 把它掏出来给我看
I was afraid that you were gonna cry and then show it to me.
别看了，那里面没有东西 那不是真的
Stop staring! There's nothing there! It's not true!
恐怕我需要证据
I'm afraid I'm gonna need proof.
快掏出来吧
Come on,whip it out.
你是我的珠穆朗玛峰
You are my Everest.
-你不必吃完它 -我要，不然接下来是什么？
-You don't have to finish. -I do. Otherwise,what's next?
今天我吃不完一只火鸡 明天我只能吃一半的三明治…
Today I can't finish a turkey,but tomorrow I eat half a PowerBar..
把剩下的东西包起来 放在冰箱？不
wrap it up and put it in the fridge? No!
我得去换条裤子，我在想什么？ 牛仔裤根本没有伸缩性
I gotta change my pants. What was I thinking? Jeans have no give.
大家来帮我洗碗 要洗的锅子真的很多
Guys,help me with the dishes. There's a lot of pots and pans.
亲爱的，我很想 但第二场比赛快开始了
Honey,I'd love to,but the second game is about to start.
对，第二场比赛 菲比队要看足球赛
Oh,yeah,the second game. More football for the Pheebster.
-哪一队要比赛？ -洛杉矶队
-Who's playing? -Los Angeles.
据我所知 洛杉矶没有美式足球队
Last time I checked,Los Angeles didn't have a football team.
我说洛杉矶吗？ 我是说以前在洛杉矶…
Did I say Los Angeles? I meant the team that used to be in Los Angeles..
现在在圣路易斯队的球队 我真的知道这件事
and is now in St. Louis. I actually knew that.
快说出 那只球队的三个球员
Okay,quick,name three players on that team.
葛瑞斯基…
Gretzky..
阿格西…
Agassi..
我是个小美女
I'm a pretty little girl.
你们看史恩麦马洪 在我的纪念册上写了什么
Listen to what Sean McMahon wrote in my yearbook senior year.
“亲爱的瑞秋，你真是个好人” 我不是女孩，我是“人”
"Dear Rach,you're such a great person." Not girl,"person."
我想你太敏感了
I think you're reading a little too much into it.
“你是个好人 关于你有小鸡鸡的事我很遗憾”
"You're a great person. Sorry about your teeny weenie."
你要我怎么做？ 你要我…
What do you want me to do..
打电话给全校的人 告诉他们那不是真的？
call everyone in the entire school and tell them it wasn't true?
-对 -顺便告诉他们我变瘦了
-Yes. -Also,tell them I'm skinny now.
还有我
Oh! Me too!
我不会打电话给任何人 那是很久以前的事了
I won't call anybody. It was a million years ago.
我不在乎 你们告诉大家我是双性人
I don't care. You told people that I was half and half!
在高中时 我没有做过任何伤害你的事
I never did anything to hurt you in high school.
那不完全是真的
That's not totally true.
-什么？ -什么？
-What? -What?
你告诉大家罗斯…
You did start that rumor about Ross..
跟50岁大的图书馆员 亚特曼太太亲亲抱抱
making out with Mrs. Altmann,our 50-year-old librarian.
你怎么知道那个的？
How did you know that?
-那是真的？ -不
-It's true? -No.
不，那是真的，我看到你们 躲在书卡目录的后面
Yes,it is. I saw you guys going at it behind the card catalog.
-你在图书馆里做什么？ -图书馆里有杂志
-Hey,what were you doing in the library? -They had magazines.
亚特曼太太，她在…
Mrs. Altmann? She also made out..
塔塔卡奇奇回泰国前一晚 也跟他耳鬓厮磨了一下
with Ta-Taka-Ki-Kek the night before he went back to Thailand.
高中时 你跟50岁的女人耳鬓厮磨？
In high school you made out with a 50-year-old woman?
-她看起来不像50岁了 -她看起来像16岁吗？
-Hey,she didn't look 50! -Did she look 16?
事实上纪念册里 有她的照片
There's a picture of her in the yearbook actually.
-哇 -她不太上相
-Wow. -She didn't photograph well!
或者她不知道 该怎么…
She probably wasn't familiar with the process..
花时间 练习坐下来当油画模特儿
having spent most of her life sitting for oil paintings.
这是怎么发生的？ 她一放学就请你吃晚餐引诱你？
How did this happen? Did she lure you to an early-bird dinner?
有一天下午我在图书馆里看书看得很晚 馆里只有我们两个
I was working late in the library one afternoon. It was just the two of us.
她需要人帮忙玩填字游戏
She needed some help with her word jumble.
事情很自然就发生了
And one thing led to another.
我得告诉你们 安妮塔非常仁慈温柔
If you must know,Anita was very gentle and tender.
希望她能得到安息
May she rest in peace.
-她不是柱着收茸呗仿穑 -只有在天气潮湿时
-Didn't she walk with a cane? -Only when it was damp!
我不相信你告诉大家这件事 大家都知道吗？
I can't believe you told people about this. Everybody knew?
-好了，我要重回俱乐部 -耶
-You know what? I'm back in the club! -Yeah!
-我要召开大会吗？ -大家都得来吗？
-Shall I call the meeting to order? -Is everybody present?
除了塔塔卡之外
With the exception of Ta-Taka.
-我要加入 -菲比
-I wanna join! -Phoebe?
抱歉，我从来没有加入过俱乐部 我没有念过高中
I'm sorry,but I never got to be in a club. I didn't go to high school.
但我们三个 可以躲在垃圾箱后面学法文
But three of us would meet behind a dumpster to learn French.
好吧 你们可以继续那个愚蠢的小俱乐部
Fine,you can have your stupid,little club.
但你对我做的事 比我对你做的事更糟糕
But what you did to me is way worse than what I did to you.
-你说我有小鸡鸡 -对
-You gave me a teeny weenie. -Yeah!
你真的太傻了 瑞秋，即使有那个谣言…
You're just being silly. Rachel,even with that rumor..
你还是最受欢迎的女孩 大家都希望能跟你一样
you were one of the most popular girls. Everyone wanted to be like you.
有个女孩太想变得跟你一样 她把棒棒糖塞进裤档里
One girl wanted to be like you so much,she stuffed her pants with a Tootsie Roll.
哇
Wow.
罗斯，要不是她的谣言 没有人会知道你是谁
And Ross,if it weren't for her rumor,no one would've known who you were.
-是她让你成名 -以老女人的情人成名
-She put you on the map. -As a romancer of the elderly.
可以看得出来亚特曼太太 她以前很漂亮
Mrs. Altmann,you can tell,she used to be pretty.
她的眼睛还是会发光
The eyes did still sparkle.
这是很久以前的事了 你们也经历过很多事
This stuff is so way in the past. You've been through so much since then.
你们的未来 还有许多更重要的事
You got so much more important stuff going on in your life.
你们不能忘了这件事吗？
Can't you just let this go?
-她说的对 -我们的孩子快出生了
-She's right. -We are having a baby together.
等一下
Hold on.
-你让她怀孕了？ -对
-You got her pregnant? -Yeah.
-你们要结婚了？ -不
-Are you getting married? -No.
你搞大她的肚子 但你不娶她，兄弟
So you knocked her up but you're not gonna marry her. Dude.
-有人要吗？ -好吧
-Anybody? -Okay.
它跟我想像中完全一样
It's exactly how I imagined it would be.
好吧，火鸡在哪里？
All right,where's that turkey?
-那是我的孕妇裤 -不，这是我的感恩节裤
-Those are my maternity pants! -No,these are my Thanksgiving pants!
好了，我吃完了
Well,that's it. I'm done.
流下了肉汗
Here come the meat sweats.
乔伊 我们非常以你为荣
Well,Joey,we're all very proud of you.
我相信 总统随时都会打电话来
I believe we can expect a call from the president any moment now.
-有什么我们可以帮忙的吗？ -不必了，但千万别压我的胃
-Anything we can do? -No. Just nobody press on my stomach.
还有，那条裤子你不用还了
You can keep those pants,by the way.
那是什么？ 那是派吗？
What you got there? What is that,pie?
-对，你要吃一点吗？ -切一小块给我就行了
-Yeah. You want some? -Just cut me a little sliver.
大一点
Little bigger.
再大一点
你害怕没派吃吗？ 切一大块给我
Are you afraid you're gonna run out? Cut me a real piece!